We've lost contact with a force that was
sent into Galia to collect raw materials.
No contact at all? Do we know the cause?
We don't.
Where was this force headed?
The Great Ravine.
The Great Ravine...
We'll move to rescue them immediately.
Right!
Let's make for Galia, at once.
Magic crystal?
Right.
To make the ideal scabbard for your sword,
I'm definitely going to need it.
But... it's been hard to get ahold of lately.
And there's no shipments incoming?
The royal army oversees the supply of
magic crystal, so I don't know the details.
Well, if there's none coming,
then we'll just go and grab it ourselves.
Fate, we've got crystal to collect.
Jade, where can I find magic crystal?
There's some in Galia, I think.
In Galia, huh?
Not a problem.
I'll go and get some.
Wait, seriously?
I'll give you a discount, then.
This is a map my master,
who was a soldier in his youth,
used to collect materials.
The spots that are marked
are pretty far south...
Near the Great Ravine.
Okay, looks like we're on a quest
to get me a scabbard!
Trap
Greed.
Yeah?
Let's use Shield Bash.
You're learning! Good for you.
Now it's our turn!
Gluttony skill has activated.
Gluttony skill has activated...
Lady Roxy.
Look at this.
Oh, my...
Right, compasses don't work here.
Then how are we supposed to
find our way to the Great Ravine?
Usually, we'd be able to navigate based on
the position of the moon and the stars...
But with these clouds?
The moon can't be seen.
Stupid clouds!
It's said that the general layout of Galia
can be judged by the density
of the orc population.
Orc population density?!
Really?
Yes.
The records say that the biggest orc
colonies are the furthest south.
So if we follow the trail of orcs,
it'll take us toward the Great Ravine.
But there are more monsters
in Galia than orcs.
Crowned beasts dwell
in this direction, as well.
We should be careful heading forward.
You're starting to really act the part.
What do you mean?
A warrior should always get proper rest
in preparation for battle!
Shut up.
What is this place?
You're...
From before!
There's so much noise, I can't hear her.
What's she saying?
Hado?!
Stop!
Stop it!
What was that?!
Greed, monsters.
And this presence... it's not orcs.
A crowned beast. More than one, actually.
Let's go!
Where are they?
Use your Night Vision skill.
Got it.
There...
Those are salamanders.
Four of them?
Switch me to the black bow.
We'll make the first attack
with petrifying magic!
Good!
Let's take another out.
Hang on, Greed.
Something's going on
with those salamanders...
Yeah... Usually, they run off
if they're hurt this badly.
They're not running, and they're not
trying to attack me in return, either.
What is this?
It's like something's controlling them.
They're being controlled?
All right, after them!
Right!
What's happening?
We've been surrounded by salamanders!
Northern! Where are you, Northern?
Lady Roxy...
I'm so sorry... They got past me...
Northern!
Look out!
The ground melted...
That's some incredible heat.
If you hurt Lady Roxy, I'll make you pay!
Magic Sword, Flamberge!
It's not working?!
Idiot! Didn't you know what'd happen using
a magic sword against salamanders?!
Are you all right, Miria?
Are you hurt?
Corpse?
Here they come!
Sharp Edge!
To get that kind of power out of
a common skill like Sharp Edge...
This guy's really something.
Corpse.
Thank you so much for aiding us.
If it weren't for you,
more of my soldiers would have died.
You should thank him, Miria.
I didn't ask for his help!
I wanted to be the one
who saved you, Lady Roxy.
You idiot!
Looks like we meet again.
I'm Mugan, the captain of this unit.
And this idiot here is Miria.
Show the man some gratitude, dammit.
Thank you so much!
This is Northern, a holy knight
assigned to Babylon.
You really saved us.
Don't worry about thanking me.
There's something I'm more concerned about.
What is that?
It looks like an emblem...
The same one is on this salamander, too.
This one, as well.
All four of them have the same
emblem on their heads...
Well, that's really suspicious,
isn't it, Lady Roxy?
What's going on here?
Crowned beasts don't usually work together.
I see...
And it was like they were all after Lady Roxy.
I'm sure that was just a coincidence.
There's no telling what can happen in Galia.
Especially in the days since
the Divine Dragon has left its lair...
This is the Great Ravine.
Thanks. I appreciate the help.
Of course.
Lucky thing we were headed
in the same direction, Sir Corpse.
We've got to hurry on to rescue
the supply unit, so if you'll excuse us...
Come on, Lady Roxy!
Well, I'll be praying for your success.
Scared of your Telepathy
skill kicking in, huh?
I had better protect Lady Roxy!
Don't get so full of yourself just because
you're kinda strong, bonehead!
You're a nasty pest, so buzz off!
Miria? What are you doing?
Honestly...
I'm sorry about her.
It's fine.
Come, let's be on our way.
Sure!
She called you a nasty pest...
Shut up!
The air's so clean here.
Like it's being purified locally somehow.
Probably an after-effect of an old battle...
A petrified monster?
It's got to have something to do
with this unique environment.
A monster graveyard, huh?
What's up? Did you find some magic crystal?
No... It's nothing.
Magic crystals are transparent and
colorless but give off a faint purple glow.
I don't think I see anything like that.
Who's that?
Eris!
She got away...
Fate. Take a look over there.
That's...!
A chimera!
Huh... it's not moving.
Probably a prototype. Take a better look.
There's no core.
You're right.
It was probably buried here
in some ancient battle...
And then, after a landslide,
its head started peeking out.
There's another area that
looks like there was a landslide.
The lay of the land has really
changed around here...
Seems like some of them managed to wake up.
Looks like three...
Is she behind this?
That's coming from the east.
That's the direction Lady Roxy
was searching in!
This seems familiar.
More monsters after Roxy!
We're never gonna find any
magic crystal at this rate!
I'm gonna protect Lady Roxy!
Miria!
No! Mugan!
Mugan!
Northern!
Corpse?
You all right?
Mugan... He was injured protecting Miria.
Northern's hurt, too.
It's not regenerating too fast.
These things don't stack up to Haniel.
These things are called chimera.
Their cores are their weakness.
Cores?
You see how there's a monster
embedded in their chest?
Yes.
That's the core that keeps
the chimera moving.
We just need to slay them. Are you ready?
Yes.
Miria, you know what to do?
Right!
Let's go!
They're trying to keep us away.
Too bad for them...
We've got Fire Resistance!
It's covering the core?
Just like I figured.
Now!
Aaron must've taught her a few things.
Die! I'm gonna die!
Someone hurry!
She's better than I thought.
Yeah. She's using Flamberge's flame
to parry the flames of the chimera...
She's got a mouth on her, but the
little lady's got a knack for fighting.
I've got this.
I let the bonehead save me again!
What a blunder!
Thanks, though!
You okay, Mugan?
Yeah...
Miria!
Lady Roxy!
Get the others to safety.
Corpse and I will deal
with the other chimera.
Right!
We'll use the same method as before.
Understood!
I've never fought alongside
Lady Roxy before...
Feels more natural than with Myne and Aaron.
Just one left.
Yes. Let's put an end to this.
You okay? You're breathing hard.
I'm still fit to fight!
It jumped?
Let's hit it when it lands.
Right!
Lady Roxy!
It might not look like it,
but I know I can tank the landing.
Understood. I'm in your care.
Yeah. I've got you.
You awake, Fate?
Greed?
Right... We must've fallen from there...
Fay...
Yes?
Lady Roxy?!
Oh, right! I remember now!
This is really, really bad!
It's gone! What the...?!
Why?!
Oh... what happened?
Oh! C-Corpse!
Forgive me.
It's fine.
Ow...
You all right?
With some rest, I will be.
That's a holy knight for you.
You can use Fireball, too?
We almost had it.
If the ground hadn't given out,
we probably could've beat that chimera.
The chimera...
Yeah.
They're apparently artificial monsters
created in Galia 4,000 years ago.
How'd things go on your end?
Did you find the supply unit?
We weren't fast enough.
Their forward base, along with the
entire force, had been burnt to ashes...
I see.
I'm curious, Corpse,
who told you about the chimera?
A surviving Galian filled me in.
A young girl with a giant axe, perhaps?
I've seen her before, in my territory.
I'd heard rumors about her
on the way to Babylon, as well.
She apparently sent a local lord flying
with that axe of hers.
W-Well, that sounds dangerous.
The rumors say she was traveling
with a young man in a skull mask...
Yeah, that's right! It was me!
I thought as much!
You seem happy about that.
Seriously... don't stare like that.
Forgive me. Something about you
reminds me of someone I know.
It does?
Yes.
He should be in the capital...
But it feels like he's right here with me.
It's so strange.
Now that we're apart,
I find myself wondering...
If the things I did for him were right.
If they were for the best.
Is Fay really happy?
He should be.
Having someone care about him as much
as you do... he ought to be plenty happy.
I would like to hope so.
You never change, Lady Roxy.
Of all the times...!
What's wrong, Corpse?
Your eye...
Don't look! Please, just don't.
Corpse!
This is awful.
And this smell... it's nearby.
There you are!
Enough!
Don't...
Don't look at me... like that!
That's...
Another one of these emblems?
Between the salamanders and now chimera...
We can be pretty sure
someone wants Roxy dead.
Roxy Hart.
She's going to die in Galia.
Eris... you'll pay for this.
Corpse?
This thing...
I took it down. Should be fine now.
I see.
Look out!
Magic crystal!
But... isn't that just a fossilized monster?
Magic crystal is made out of such monsters.
Were you searching for it
without knowing that?
No wonder we didn't find any.
Lady Roxy!
I'm so glad you're okay!
I'm pleased to see you're all safe.
Death March
"Death March."